Guide to the Robert A. M. Stern Architects Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project records for 1987-1989, 1987-2001; Accession 2014-M-052
  - Roger Tory Peterson Institute (Jamestown, NY) (89007), 1989-1994
    - Project drawings
      - Color studies (Box 127)
      - Design, presentation, and monograph drawings (Box 128)
      - Working drawings (construction) (Box 129)
      - Working drawings (preliminary) (Box 130)
      - Small-scale design and presentation drawings (Box 173, Folder 170-172)
    - Project sketches (Box 173, Folder 169)
  - Residence on Kiawah Island (Kiawah Island, SC) (89008), 1989-1991
    - Project file (Box 38, Folder 711-716)
    - Project images (Box 61, Folder 117)
    - Project drawings
      - Design and monograph drawings (Box 130)
      - Presentation drawings (Box 131)
      - Project sketches (Box 173, Folder 173-174)
  - The Country Club for the Villages at Rocky Fork (New Albany, OH) (89009), 1989
    See Also: 89010, 89011
    - Project file
      - Correspondence, memoranda, and regulation (Box 38, Folder 717-720)
      - Program background, specifications, and lighting (Box 39, Folder 721-723)
    - Project images (Box 61, Folder 118)
    - Project drawings
      - Color studies (Box 131)
      - Design and presentation drawings (Box 132)
      - Working drawings (Box 133)
      - Monograph drawings (Box 174, Folder 175)
    - Project sketches (Box 174, Folder 176)
  - Master Plan for the Villages at Rocky Fork (New Albany, OH) (89010), 1989
    See Also: 89009, 89011
    - Project file (Box 39, Folder 724)
    - Project images (Box 61, Folder 119)
    - Project drawings (Box 134)
    - Project sketches (Box 174, Folder 177)
  - Houses for the Villages at Rocky Fork (New Albany, OH) (89011), 1989
    See Also: 89009, 89010
    - Project images (Box 61, Folder 120)
    - Project drawings (Box 134)
    - Project sketches (Box 174, Folder 178-180)
  - Bed and Bath Furnishings for Atelier Martex (89012), 1989-1994
    - Project file (Box 39, Folder 725-742)
    - Project images (Box 61, Folder 121)
    - Project drawings (Box 134)
  - Furniture for Hickory Business Furniture (89013), 1989-1997
    See Also: 90003, A03005
    - Project file (Box 40, Folder 743-749)
    - Project images (Box 61, Folder 122)
    - Project drawings
      - Small drawings (Box 40, Folder 744-746)
      - Design drawings (Box 134)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 174, Folder 181)
  - Meadowbrook II (Hempstead, NY) (89014)
    See Also: 85097
    - Project file (Box 40, Folder 750-758)
    - Project images (Box 61, Folder 123)
    - Project drawings (Box 135)
    - Project sketches (Box 174, Folder 182)
  - Imax Theatre Study (New York, NY) (89015), 1989
    See Also: 87029
    - Project file (Box 40, Folder 759)
    - Project images (Box 61, Folder 124)
    - Project drawings (Box 175, Folder 184)
    - Project sketches (Box 175, Folder 183)
  - The Gables (Bloomfield Hills, MI) (89016), 1989-1991
    See Also: 87025. This project began as part of number 87025.
    - Project file
      - Correspondence, field reports and memoranda (Box 40, Folder 760-766)
      - Furnishings, correspondence, specifications, and miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 768-774)
    - Project images
      - Jul 1990 - Jan 1992 (Box 61, Folder 125)
      - Oct 1989 - Jun 1990 (Box 62, Folder 126)
    - Project drawings
      - Small drawings (Box 40, Folder 767)
      - Monograph and working drawings (Box 135)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 175, Folder 186)
    - Project sketches (Box 175, Folder 185)
  - Residence in Bloomfield Hills (Bloomfield Hills, MI) (89017), 1989-1990
    - Project file (Box 41, Folder 775-781)
    - Project images (Box 62, Folder 127)
    - Project drawings (Box 136)
    - Project sketches (Box 175, Folder 187)
  - Riverwalk, Chevron Land and Development Corporation (San Diego, CA) (89019), 1989-1991
    See Also: 91021. Project continued under number 91021.
    - Project file (Box 41, Folder 782-788)
    - Project images (Box 62, Folder 128)
    - Project drawings (Box 136)
    - Project sketches (Box 175, Folder 188-189)
  - Alterations and Additions to the Edwards-Smyth House (Charleston, SC) (89020), 1989-1990
    - Project file (Box 42, Folder 789-797)
    - Project images (Box 62, Folder 129)
    - Project drawings (Box 137)
    - Project sketches (Box 175, Folder 190-191)
  - Halpern Residence II (Westport, CT) (89021), 1989-1990
    - Project file (Box 42, Folder 798-803)
    - Project images (Box 62, Folder 130)
    - Project drawings
      - Design, presentation drawings, and record prints (Box 137)
      - Working drawings (Box 138)
    - Project sketches (Box 175, Folder 192-194)
  - Fort Worth Town Square (Fort Worth, TX) (89022), 1989
    - Project images (Box 62, Folder 131)
    - Project drawings (Box 138)
    - Project sketches (Box 176, Folder 195)
  - Pierson Lakes Development (Sterlington, NY) (89023), 1989
    - Project file (Box 42, Folder 804)
    - Project images (Box 62, Folder 132)
    - Project drawings (Box 138)
    - Project sketches (Box 176, Folder 196)
  - Concord Walk Hotel (Charleston, SC) (89024), 1989-1990
    - Project file
      - Reports, billings, project statistics, and miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 805-818)
      - Landscape, graphics, pricing, publicity, and miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 819-830)
    - Project images (Box 62, Folder 133)
    - Project drawings (Box 139)
    - Project sketches (Box 176, Folder 197)
  - Addition to a Cottage (East Hampton, NY) (89025), 1989-1993
    See Also: 79101
    - Project file (Box 43, Folder 831-843)
    - Project images (Box 62, Folder 134-136)
    - Project drawings (Box 76)
      - Small drawings (Box 43, Folder 832)
      - Monograph and working drawings (Box 140)
    - Project sketches (Box 176, Folder 198)
  - Anglebrook Golf Club (Somers, NY) (89026), 1989-1998
    - Project file
      - Pre-design and pre-construction services, correspondence, and miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 844-858)
      - Correspondence, minutes, and miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 859-869)
      - Specifications, reports, correspondence, publicity, and miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 870-885)
    - Project images
      - Jan 1990 - Jul 1998 (Box 62, Folder 137)
      - Sep 1989 - May 1998 (Box 63, Folder 138-139)
    - Project drawings
      - Small drawings (Box 46, Folder 884)
      - Color studies and construction set (1) (Box 140)
      - Construction set (2) and design development set (Box 141)
      - Design, presentation, lighting design, and preliminary set (Box 142)
    - Project sketches (Box 24, Folder 199-201)
  - Mar-a-Lago Apartment Building, Surfers Paradise (Queensland, Australia) (89027), 1989
    - Project file (Box 47, Folder 886)
    - Project images (Box 63, Folder 140)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation and miscellaneous mylar drawings (Box 143)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 177, Folder 203)
    - Project sketches (Box 177, Folder 202-203)
  - Morton Street Ventilation Building (New York, NY) (89028), 1989
    - Project file (Box 47, Folder 887)
    - Project images (Box 63, Folder 141)
    - Project drawings
      - Color studies and presentation drawings (Oct 1989 - Nov 1989) (Box 143)
      - Presentation drawings (Dec 1989) (Box 144)
    - Project sketches (Box 177, Folder 204)
  - Boyd Lighting (89029), 1989-1990
    - Project file (Box 47, Folder 890)
    - Project drawings (Box 47, Folder 888-889)
  - House at Apaquogue (East Hampton, NY) (89030), 1989-1994
    See Also: 89030.03, 89030.04, A10044
    - Project file
      - Correspondence, field reports, memoranda, pbulicity, specifications, and miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 891-907)
      - Landscape, mechanical, structural, and miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 908-915)
    - Project images (Box 63, Folder 142-144)
    - Project drawings
      - Small drawings (Box 47, Folder 898)
      - Design, presentation, and monograph drawings (Box 144)
      - Working drawings, sheets A1-A65 (Box 145)
      - Working drawings, E1-E4, M1-M5, P1-P5, L1-L7, L12 (Box 146)
    - Project sketches (Box 177, Folder 205-207)
  - House at Apaquogue, Garage Addition and Terrace Extension (East Hampton, NY) (89030.03), 1996
    See Also: 89030, 89030.04, A10044
    - Project file (Box 48, Folder 916)
    - Project drawings (Box 146)
  - Addition to House at Apaquogue (East Hampton, NY) (89030.04), 1999-2001
    See Also: 89030, 89030.03, A10044
    - Project file (Box 48, Folder 917-923)
    - Project images (Box 63, Folder 145)
    - Project drawings (Box 146)
  - Na Pali Haweo, Kamehame Ridge (Oahu, HI) (89031), 1989-1991
    - Project file
      - Correspondence, memoranda, publicity, and contracts (Box 48, Folder 924-928)
      - Regulation, program background, correspondence, specifications, and miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 930-938)
    - Project images (Box 63, Folder 146)
    - Project drawings
      - Small drawings (Box 48, Folder 929)
      - Design drawings (Box 146)
      - Presentation and working drawings (Box 147)
    - Project sketches (Box 178, Folder 208)
  - Eisner Residence, Bel Air (Bel Air, CA) (89032), 1989-1992
    See Also: 89032.06
    - Project file (Box 49, Folder 939)
    - Project images (Box 64, Folder 147)
    - Project drawings
      - Design, presentation, working, and record sets (Box 148)
      - Small-scale presentation drawings (Box 178, Folder 210)
    - Project sketches (Box 178, Folder 209-210)
  - House Renovation (Bel Air, CA) (89032.06), 2000-2001
    See Also: 89032
    - Project file
      - Pre-design and pre-construction services, correspondence, and miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 940-945)
      - Minutes, specifications, correspondence, reports, and miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 946-962)
      - In-house, interiors, and interiors specifications (Box 51, Folder 963-969)
    - Project images (Box 64, Folder 148)
    - Project drawings (Box 149)
  - Pool and Pergola on Kiawah Island (Kiawah Island, SC) (89035), 1989-1990
    - Project file (Box 51, Folder 970-979)
    - Project images (Box 64, Folder 149)
    - Project drawings (Box 149)
    - Project sketches (Box 178, Folder 211)
  - Kiawah Beach Club (Kiawah Island, SC) (89037), 1989-1990
    See Also: 92030
    - Project file
      - Correspondence, memoranda, and publicity (Box 51, Folder 980-983)
      - Contracts, program background, specifications, and miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 984-990)
    - Project images (Box 64, Folder 150)
    - Project drawings (Box 86)
      - Small drawings (Box 52, Folder 985)
      - Color studies, design, presentation, and working drawings (Box 150)
    - Project sketches (Box 179, Folder 212-213)
  - Washington State Labor and Industries Building (Olympia, WA) (89038), 1990
    - Project file (Box 52, Folder 991-1000)
    - Project images (Box 64, Folder 151)
    - Project drawings
      - Color studies, design, monograph, and presentation drawings (Box 151)
      - Small-scale design and presentation drawings (Box 179, Folder 215)
    - Project sketches (Box 179, Folder 214-215)
  - Apartment House (Chicago, IL) (89039), 1989-1991
    - Project file (Box 52, Folder 1001-1006)
    - Project images (Box 64, Folder 152)
    - Project drawings
      - Small drawings (Box 52, Folder 1003)
      - Colors studies, monograph, and presentation drawings (Box 152)
    - Project sketches (Box 179, Folder 216-218)
  - Lansdowne Development/Loudon County Civic Center (Landsdowne, VA) (89040), 1989-1990
    - Project file (Box 52, Folder 1007)
    - Project drawings (Box 152)
    - Project sketches (Box 179, Folder 219)
- Project records for 1990-1992, 1990-2001; Accession 2016-M-0097
  These records document the design work of the firm begun in 1990, 1991, and 1992. There are multiple inter-related projects during this time period and in some cases there is work related to projects from other time periods. Whenever possible "See Also" references have been included.
  In general the records are made up of drawings, files and imagery. Models and artwork associated with these projects remain with RAMSA.
  - Interior Theming, Sequoia Lodge, Euro Disneyland (Marne le Vallee, France) (90001), project file, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Access restricted.
  - Disney's Boardwalk Village and Hotel, Walt Disney World (Lake Buena Vista, FL) (90002), 1990-1992
    This is an unbuilt project. Work under RAMSA project number 93004 was eventually realized on this site.
    See Also: 93004
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - To/from client (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
      - Associate Architect (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Minutes, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
      - Specifications (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Fees (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - In-house (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation drawings
        - Mylar originals (Box 53)
        - Mylar originals and prints (Box 54)
        - Prints (Box 55)
      - Working drawings
        - Mylar originals, architectural schematic (Box 56)
        - Mylar originals, architectural schematic (Box 57)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Project sketches (Box 118, Folder 1-4)
  - Textiles for HBF (90003), project images, 1990-2001 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Town Square at The Falls (Raleigh, NC) (90005), project drawings, 1990 (Box 57)
  - Town Square -- Plano (Plano, TX) (90006), project drawings, 1990 (Box 57)
  - Buford House Landscape (Irvington, NY) (90007), project images, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - St. Barnabas Memorial Garden (Irvington, NY) (90008), 1990-1992
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Project drawings (Box 57)
  - Espace Euro Disney (Villiers-sur-Marne, France) (90012), 1990-1991
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Project drawings (Box 58)
    - Project sketches (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Gilliam Residence (Kiawah Island, SC) (90014), 1990-1991
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Project drawings (Box 58)
    - Project sketches (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Old Merchant's House Table Ornament (90015), project images (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Custom House (Boston, MA) (90016), 1990
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Project sketches (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk Center Theater (Norfolk, VA) (90017), 1990
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Project drawings (Box 58)
    - Project sketches (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Chiburi Lake Golf Resort (Chiburi, Japan) (90019), 1990
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation drawings (Box 58)
      - Working drawings (Box 59)
    - Project sketches (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Kitsuregawa Golf Club House (Tochigi Prefecture, Japan) (90020), 1990-1991
    See Also: 90021
    - Project file (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Project drawings (Box 59)
    - Project sketches (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Kitsuregawa Golf Club Inn (Tochigi Prefecture, Japan) (90021), 1990
    See Also: 90020
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Project drawings (Box 59)
    - Project sketches (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Greenbrier at West Village Golf Resort (Fukushima Prefecture, Japan) (90022), 1990-1995
    - Project file (Box 2, Folder 19-37)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 13-15)
    - Project drawings
      - Monograph drawings (Box 59)
      - Presentation drawings and working drawings, design development (Box 60)
      - Working drawings, design development (Box 61)
      - Working drawings, design development and schematic design (Box 62)
    - Project sketches (Box 119, Folder 13-16)
  - Residence in the Midwest (Hunting Valley, OH) (90023), 1990-1993
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - To/from client (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Structural (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Mechanical, electrical, and plumbing (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Soil engineers (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Surveyor (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Construction (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Landscape (Box 3, Folder 47-48)
      - Minutes (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Specifications (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Pricing (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Millwork (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Doors and windows (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Stone (Box 3, Folder 54, 62)
      - Hardware (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Electrical (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Security (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - Shingles (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Equipment (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Rebar (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - Concrete (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - To contractor, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 63-64)
      - To contractor, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - From contractor (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Field reports (Box 4, Folder 67-68)
      - Change orders (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - Substantial completion (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - Legal/arbitration (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - Office schedules and project costing (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - In-house, SK drawings (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 16-19)
    - Project drawings
      - Design drawings, presentation drawings (Box 62)
      - Monograph drawings and working drawings (Box 63)
      - Working drawings (Box 64)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - Project sketches (Box 120, Folder 17-20)
  - Izumidai Resort (Izu Peninsula, Japan) (90024), 1990
    - Project file (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Project images (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Project drawings (Box 64)
    - Project sketches (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn Law School (90025) (New York, NY), 1990
    See Also: 85048, 86024 This project number is directly related to RAMSA project number 86024 (the first schemes/phases of a Brooklyn Law School addition). The project was eventually built, incorporating significant elements of the 86024 work, under this project number.
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 4, Folder 75)
      - To client (Box 4, Folder 76)
      - From client (Box 4, Folder 77)
      - Authorities (permits, filing, and approvals) (Box 4, Folder 78)
      - Cost consultants (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Associated architect (Box 4, Folder 80-86)
      - Structural (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Mechanical, electrical, and plumbing (Box 4, Folder 88)
      - Landscape (Box 4, Folder 89-90)
      - Lighting (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - Kitchen (Box 5, Folder 92)
      - Acoustic (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - Expediter/code consultant (Box 5, Folder 94)
      - Elevator (Box 5, Folder 95)
      - Client meetings (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - Consultant coordination meetings (Box 5, Folder 97-99)
      - Site meetings (Box 5, Folder 100-102)
      - Pre-construction memos (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - Specifications (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - Materials (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Bid and quotations (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - Nominated suppliers and sub-contractors (Box 5, Folder 107)
      - To construction manager/contractor (Box 5, Folder 108-111)
      - From construction manager/contractor (Box 5, Folder 112)
      - Field reports (Box 5, Folder 113)
      - Substantial completion (Box 5, Folder 114)
      - Fees (Box 5, Folder 115)
      - Publicity (Box 5, Folder 116)
      - In-house - FSK drawings (Box 5, Folder 117)
      - Furnishings (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 21-25)
    - Project drawings
      - Color studies (Box 64)
      - Furniture, lighting, plaza renovation, presentation, and working - schematic design (Box 65)
      - Working drawings - SKs (Box 66)
      - Working drawings - SKs (Box 67)
    - Project sketches (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - The House That Bob Built (90026), 1990-1991
    - Project file (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Additions to Points of View (Mount Desert Island, ME) (90027), 1990
    See Also: 75062, 92024, 92024.01
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Project sketches (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - "New York: Yesterday,Today, and Tomorrow" Metropolitan Home Showhouse II (90029)
    - Project file (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Project drawings (Box 67)
    - Project sketches (Box 121, Folder 25)
  - China for Haviland (90030), 1990-1991
    - Project file (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Project drawings and sketches (Box 121, Folder 26-28)
  - Banana Republic (Chicago, IL) (90032), 1990-1991
    - Project file (Box 6, Folder 122-127)
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 30-31)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation drawings (Box 67)
      - Working drawings (Box 68)
    - Project sketches (Box 121, Folder 29-30)
  - The Turning Point Competition (Amstelveen, Netherlands) (90033), 1990-1991
    - Project file (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Project drawings (Box 69)
    - Project sketches (Box 121, Folder 31)
  - RAMS Apartment Renovation (New York, NY) (90034), 1990-1993
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Project sketches (Box 121, Folder 32)
  - Banana Republic on Lexington Avenue (New York, NY) (90035), project images, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Denver Public Library (Denver, CO) (90036), 1990-1991
    - Project file (Box 6, Folder 129-136)
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 35-36)
    - Project drawings (Box 69)
    - Project sketches (Box 121, Folder 33)
  - Tram Shelter, Newport Bay Club, Euro Disneyland (90037), project file, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - CEO Compound and Ranch (Portola Valley, CA) (90038), project file, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Hillcrest Plaza (San Diego, CA) (90039), project images, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Chile Hotel (Chile) (90042), project images, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    This is an unbuilt project
  - Del Mar Civic Center (Del Mar, CA) (90043), 1990-1991
    - Project file (Box 6, Folder 139-145)
    - Project images (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation and working drawings (Box 70)
      - Small-scale presentation drawings (Box 121, Folder 35)
    - Project sketches (Box 121, Folder 34)
  - Disney Regional Shopping Center Competition (Orlando, FL) (91001), 1991
    - Project file (Box 7, Folder 146-150)
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Project drawings (Box 71)
    - Project sketches (Box 122, Folder 36-38)
  - Columbus Medical Office Building (Columbus, IN) (91002), 1991-1993
    See Also: 92019
    - Project file (Box 7, Folder 151-168)
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Project drawings
      - Originals (Box 71)
      - Record set, for construction (Box 72)
    - Project sketches (Box 122, Folder 39)
  - Tivoli Museum and Apartments (Tokyo, Japan) (91003), 1991
    - Project file (Box 8, Folder 169-181)
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation and working drawings (Box 72)
      - Working drawings (Box 73)
      - Small-scale design and presentation drawings (vellum) (Box 123, Folder 42)
    - Project sketches (Box 122, Folder 40-41)
  - Mountain Residence (Yamanahi Prefecture, Japan) (91005), 1991
    - Project file (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Project drawings (Box 74)
    - Project sketches (Box 123, Folder 43)
  - Alterations to the Catlin House (Greenwich, CT) (91006), 1991
    See Also: 84258, 86069
    - Project file (Box 8, Folder 183)
    - Project drawings (Box 74)
  - Teleconferencing at Offices for Capital Research Company (New York, NY) (91007), project file, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 184)
    See Also: 87015
  - Tram, Euro Disneyland (91009), 1991
    See Also: 88018, 88018.03, 88018.04
    - Project file (Box 8, Folder 185)